Visit turkision.com for more!
Send my regards and respect
to the wise men of Turks.
As you order, Osman Bey.
Hold on, my Shahzade.
Whoever sets their eyes on what
is mine will bring their own deaths.
There is nothing which is yours.
You are talking to Amir Gorklu Khan!
Leave him! Leave!
I swear we will drive all
of you out of these lands!
Holofira, don't be afraid.
We’ll get out of here. We never bow.
My Shahzade, hold on! We will be saved!
Orhan!
Osman's baby! What you said will never happen!
If you weren't the bait,
...you wouldn't have lived this long.
Attention! Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you!
-Peace be upon you too!
Alps! We got some intelligence last night.
And we sent messengers
to the lords in the borders.
"Boran.
My Bey.
-What's the situation?
-The messengers arrived, my Bey.
-The lords will be where you ordered.
-Well.
-I think the lords will play a trick, my Bey.
-They will. Absolutely, they will.
But we will play a bigger trick.
When you accomplish your
duties, the lords will have to obey us.
We won't be unprepared.
My Bey, what will happen when the lords obey?
What is a state?
If those under your command are only your people,
...you can grow bigger.
You can be a bey and then a beylic.
But if all of them are under your command
...if you see their people as your own people,
...if you collect taxes and protect them,
...then you can be a state
and then a state of world!
Both Seljuks and Mongolians did so.
-If Allah permits, we will do the same.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
My Bey, should we trust heathens?
Samil, how do you know heathens
will always remain heathens?
Who knows? Maybe, Allah
will warm their hearts up...
...and make them join Islam, the right way.
-If Allah permits my Bey.
-If Allah permits
But if they keep being treacherous,
...I won't avoid beheading
them. You should know that.
Keep your hearts at ease!
For sure...
..we will be victorious.
Osman's dynasty will be victorious!
Osmanli Beylic will be victorious!
Osmanli Beylic! Osmanli Beylic!
We'll go meet the lords with Boran and the alps.
Konur, you will take action.
Sisters will be with you.
Your duty will be tough. But remember.
If you can't finish the duty on time,
...then our plan will fail.
Don't be worrying, my Bey. There will be a
battle. We will make the lords fight Mongolians.
Thank you.
-Come on then! Everybody get to their duties!
-Yes, my Bey!
My Bey, what about Orhan Bey?
Turks can be taken prisoners
but never remain prisoners.
-Sure, my Bey.
-Come on, alps.
Hold on until Osman arrives.
When your father comes,
...your blood will flow on the ground together.
It's not that easy.
It is not that easy.
Nokers, chain this baby.
Apparently, he wants to move.
You won't be able to get out of this hell, baby.
You will burn to ashes here.
Don't look at me like that. I'm good.
This is because of me. All because of me.
-You shouldn't have come alone, Orhan.
-I go...
...wherever you go Lord's daughter.
If we die, we die together
and we live together if we live.
Come on, alps. Come on.
-Are the swords ready?
-Everything is ready, my Bey.
-Thank you. Aykurt!
-My Bey.
Increase the numbers of
patrols in the headquarters.
As you order, my Bey.
-Did the tricksters get informed?
-Yes. They'll be here, my Bey.
Alright then. Come on, warriors!
Get on horses! Time is limited!
-Come on.
-As you order, my Bey.
As you order, my Bey.
They will be here.
You stay here. We go after them. Come on.
Tell me. What bothers your mind?
Why are we doing this, my Bey?
Our other moves aren't enough
to overwhelm Gorklu Khan.
Not enough for now. Then...
...we will change the way.
If he is making a bigger move,
...then we will make a bigger fight!
Who makes the fight bigger doesn't matter!
But we will win the fight. And I won't
leave Holofira and Orhan to them.
My Bey, will we trust them?
It's too late to think about it.
This is fight of life and death.
We'll always keep our eyes on them. If
they betray, we'll take their everything.
Well, my Bey... Will they trust us?
They will.
They'll have nothing else to do.
They will have nothing else to do.
Come on!
Osman Bey's success depends on our success.
Byzantine caravan is just a little ahead.
They're having a short rest in Karasu.
We'll go there. They won't send us back.
Konur Bey, they're coming.
-This hatun?
-Daughter of Leo, one of Christian merchants.
She'll be with us in this action.
Okay. Mongolians must be
about to arrive. Stand on alert.
-Okay, Konur Bey.
-Come on.
Come here. Osman Bey made a good trick for you.
-Why did Osman want to meet us?
-Don't be afraid, Lord Valentin.
My army is waiting at the food of Kizildag.
The soldiers are prepared for anything.
We can destroy him here.
Osman's lineage will vanish here.
He must be about to arrive!
Nokers, come on!
Flare up the flames of hell!
Commander, scouts brought
news. They saw the princess.
Konur Bey, one of Osman's
beys, and his alps are with them.
They are moving towards Karasu.
They are disguised as crusaders.
That dog Konur. They're setting up trickery.
-How do you know this Karacelasun?
-Emir Gorklu Khan.
Byzantine is setting up a camp towards Karasu.
It seems they're hiding the princess in disguise.
That is why we couldn't find them all this time.
There is only one thing that
needs to be done, Karacelasun.
Even if they're disguised as crusaders..
..the spilled blood will be Turks'.
Go strike them! Tear them apart.
Bring the princess to me.
Osman. So you're playing tricks.
To you and those behind you..
I will bring them Hadhrat Emir.
If you don't bring them,
do not bother coming back.
Nokers! Come on, we leave now!
Tong Chu.
Prepare the horses.
We will go elsewhere.
Are you hurt badly?
All this pain will go away..
..the moment you smile at me, Holofira.
However, do not worry.
We will get out of this place.
What? How, Orhan?
This is hell. They are too many, can't you see?
I will find a way.
They're coming!
I thought you called us here
to hand the princess over.
-I don't see the princess.
-I won't give her to you.
Did you lure us into an ambush, Osman Bey?
An ambush?
If I wanted harm for you..
-..I would give the princess to Mongols.
-Osman Bey, know this well.
My army is waiting near our location.
Do not try to play any tricks.
So your army is nearby.
Are you threatening me?
I came here to talk to you. Not to strike you..
..not to kill you.
First, take these. Boran.
What is this?
These are plans to take our forts.
-How can this be?
-The Emperor sold you out.
He is promising not only
the princess to mongols..
..but also your forts.
You got out of the frying
pan right into the fire.
However, you are still not aware of it.
I won’t hand over my fort
and my family to mongols!
The Emperor already did, not me.
Are you hoping to deceive
us with these false documents?
The Emperor would never sell us out!
I've heard there is not even a
single bey of Turks left behind you.
Everyone turned their backs
to you. You are hoping to..
..pull your enemy to your side as a last resort.
I won't show mercy to that kind of Osman!
-Osman!
-Lord!
I said I came here to talk.
However, you are trying to get yourself killed.
Do not test my patience.
We have one shot at this. No room for mistakes.
When mongols are in position, you
will ride your horses to byzantians.
Do not forget, we only have one purpose.
Making Byzantine and Mongols fight each other.
-Okay.
-Come on.
-Where is the princess?
-With crusader-disguised alps.
-What about our scouts?
-They are after them, commander.
Osman!
Commander, they are on the move that way!
My nokers, come on!
We will attack as soon as
the mongol enters the camp.
When Karacelasun see us, he will
be sure the crusaders side with us.
Come on alps, to horses. Quickly.
“Soldiers, defensive positions!
-Come on!
Mongols are after us!
Commander, mongols are after us. Help us!
Protect those who are with us, soldiers!
Come on!
Where is the princess? Bring me the princess!
Nokers, have their heads!
Soldier, inform the Lord that
mongols have ambushed us!
The Lord will know mongols as
their enemy and Osman Bey as ally.
-Did soldiers send a word?
-They flew a pigeon.
-It will arrive soon, If Allah permits.
-Okay.
Come on.
Now, they planned their
every move to have your forts..
..your castles after defeating us.
And you are still here
swinging your swords at me.
You will either walk with me..
..or we will all see what
happens to you after us.
You do not have any other choice.
You too, Lord.
Those documents, those markings are all real.
Take them, you ask about them.
You do not have to answe quickly as well.
However, you Lord. This is my last warning.
Do not make any mistakes again.
Do not forget this. I am not
the hopeless one here, it is you.
-Sir, the troops has sent word.
-Say it!
“Mongols have attacked.
-Who attacked?
Karacelasun, the commander of Gorklu Khan.
-So they started now!
-Osman Bey speaks the truth.
You are telling us the mongols
will attack, and they immediately do.
-How can we believe this, Osman Bey?
-Do you think..
..I would cooperate with Karacelasun..
..who has been attacking
me and my people for so long?
You dog Konur.
-You lived long.
-Is that so?
I've been thinking the same about you.
Commander, we are losing!
Tomorrow or sooner, I will have your lives!
Death is our ultimate union.
You think about yourself.
My nokers, we will fall back. Come on!
The only thing you know is
running away, you degenerate dog.
Soldier!
-Where are the ones who took shelter?
-They're gone, sir.
-Was the Lord informed?
-Yes, sir.
Now tell me Turk. Why did you help us?
You will learn that from your Lord, Commander.
Ilkhanids and Byzantium made an agreement.
And they will make you pay for this.
You will either listen to me...
...or I will leave you to your fate.
Soldiers!
Alright, Osman Bey. What do you want from us?
Unity, loyalty and tax.
-What tax Osman Bey?
-From now on, you will give me the same taxes...
...that you gave to the Seljuks...
...and the Ilkhanate.
-Who do you think...
I am the state which
protects you from the furor of...
...Mongols.
I resisted all the oppression
coming from the East.
From now on..
...you will show us the same respect...
...you showed to Byzantium and Ilkhanids.
And I will protect your people,
like I protected them until this day.
Make your decision now. But remember...
...Byzantium turned away from you.
If you still want to exist the state of Turks...
...will protect you.
I will be waiting for those who choose
us to join my table in Yenisehir tonight.
Safely.
Alps are ready and waiting at the exit
of Yenisehir. They are waiting for orders.
Let's leave before we lose any more time.
We will save Orhan and Holofira from Mongols.
Malhun Hatun! Bala Hatun!
We received news from our watchmen.
Saadet Hatun is coming to Yenisehir!
It's not the right time!
We know what Saadet's
intention is. It is to cause problems.
Malhun. Take care of Saadet.
She is coming here to cause problems.
No Bala! Orhan is in danger!
Mother! Mother! Bala mother!
-I will come with you.
-Fatma!
Not now! -Mother! No..
I cannot wait here when my brother is there.
It is time. Let me go.
Don't worry. You can deal with her.
Don't worry, we will take
Orhan and Holofira safely.
Saadet must not hear about Orhan and Holofira.
-Don't forget informing me.
-Don't worry.
The children are entrusted to you.
Be careful. -Come, Fatma.
Come on. -Let's not lose time!
Come on!
Come on, Alps! Sisters...
May Allah help you. -Come on!
May Allah protect you.
Nokers! It is time to eat!
Holofira... When I give you the sign...
..you will call the archer noker to your side.
-How will you get rid of those chains?
There is a way.
Orhan, what did you do?
Come on... Now.
Noker!
We are a bit hungry.
-Some water and bread.
-Hunger is hard, huh?
Good, good... Good.
Emir Hadhrat does not want you to die.
Here, eat. You must be hungry.
Holofira. Lower your head.
Come.
Come on! Run!
Have you heard about Cerkutay?
Did he admit that he was a spy?
-No, Saadet Hatun...
-Someone will hear it.
-No they won't.
No one will hear if I don't want them to hear.
Now..
You will do as I say, Ulgen.
-That Princess...
-Will you use me now?
You want Cerkutay to die.
You want Ghazi to grow up without a father.
What happened, Saadet Hatun?
Why did you come?
We missed Ghazi. We came here to ask Ulgen
to bring him to the frontiers' marketplace.
Did you come all that way to say this?
No. I have come to question you...
...for blocking the way to our marketplace
and dissuading the merchants who came to us.
We are the ones who can
question others here, Saadet Hatun.
Those merchants and the goods
belong to us! Any other questions?
That's what suits you. Banditry.
But we always teach bandits where to stop.
Saadet Hatun..
You better leave when you are still alive.
Or else I will..
Those meaningless threats do not scare me.
If you make our merchants go back again...
...we will do what we need to do.
And this is my last word to you.
We haven't said our last words yet, Saadet.
Are we going to switch places every day?
We'll do so for a while, Princess.
You're so afraid, right? Switch
places as much as you want.
They will find you and you will be punished.
It's not out of fear, it's
just a precaution, Princess.
My Shahzade, we were a little wait
not to leave any traces, forgive us.
No problem, Bayindir Bey. I
came early to take a look around.
-Welcome, Princess.
-Am I going to stay here, Shahzade?
It’s not worthy of you, of course.
Forgive us. But,
we put everything you might need inside.
I will not stay long. They
will find me soon, after all.
No. You'll be our guest for a long time.
Princess.
The disgraces of Gok Tengri.
If you cannot find
that puppy's woman
I'll burn this place down!
We have sent our nokers all
around Hadhrat Emir. They'll find her.
If you don't bring her...
Where is the Princess Karacelasun?
You embarrassed us, Karacelasun.
Where is my Princess?
We were trapped, Hadhrat
Emir. Osman is after bigger plans.
I told you not to come to me
if you don't bring the Princess.
Cut my head, Hadhrat Emir.
Who are you to decide when your head will be cut?
You will live as long as I want you to.
Now, let's go.
I want all the information
about Osman when I come back.
Get the horses ready.
We will go to Yakup Bey. I'll deal with it.
Cerkutay.
You can go and track her down
or find out from Osman's palace.
-You will find that Princess.
-Let’s see if you're really with us.
Which way did you go, Bayindir Bey.
You think you can hide traces from me?
These traces are lighter,
it belongs to the Princess.
You can't handle my scouting, Bayindir Bey.
Maybe Osman Bey still doesn't trust Cerkutay?
Would you trust him if you were him?
If someone betrays once, he does it
again. No one deserves a second chance.
Come on, Gonca.
If someone betrays once,
he does it again. Is that so?
Come on.
Your hand does not seem well, we need to stop.
-I'm all right Holofira, come on.
-No!
First we will deal with your hand.
You think about me too much daughter of the Lord.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
It was my fault, why did
I think about you at all?
There's no need to talk about
why, Holofira. We're in love, after all.
Take cover behind the trees!
-Are you all right?
-I'm all right my Shahzade.
-Surrender, Orhan.
-We will not surrender to these dastards.
-You have nowhere else to go.
-We will never give up!
Let all of them come.
Holofira.
Orhan, stop!
Hatun will die if you don't surrender.
Never! Do not touch her!
We will not go to Gorklu Khan
before we capture you. Do not resist.
All right! All right, let her go.
We have arrived, son. We have arrived.
Are you all right?
-We're all right.
-We're all right Bala Ana.
-You don't have any wounds, right?
-Nothing important.
You arrived right on time.
-I was so afraid, brother.
-Sister.
Sister, you couldn't help yourself
and came after me, is that so?
She'll be a strong sister.
You will need to protect
yourself well during the training.
We'll see. We'll see.
Come on. We will ride our horses to
the place we decided with my Osman Bey.
Osman Bey.
-Peace be upon you, Yunus Emre.
-Peace be upon you too, Osman Bey.
You are coming from clearing
the thorn on your way, huh?
Yes. But thanks to Allah He let me see you here.
Join me.
I made soup. Drink some.
I can't turn down your soup and words. Thank you.
Heathens will make many plans.
Believer will trust the Best of Planners...
...and ruin those plans.
Just like the Messenger of
Allah (PBUH) and his companions.
They performed an assassination
against our Prophet (PBUH)...
...but when they arrived in there,
they found Hadhrat Ali (R.A.) instead.
Their plan failed.
In the Treaty of al-Hudaybiya, they said...
..."if anyone comes to Medina from
Mecca, you will send them back."
"But we will accept those who leave Islam and
come back to the religion of their ancestors."
Our Prophet (PBUH) accepted
these terms seeming disadvantageous.
And the number of Muslims in
Mecca increased thanks to that.
Actually, the conquest of Mecca...
...got started with this treaty.
Well, Osman Bey...
You have a way to go and a guide.
Although the names of heathens change,
...their hostility remains the same.
Yes.
As long as you walk on the right way...
...and holds the rope of Allah tightly,
...you will always be victorious.
And you will ruin all their plans one by one.
For sure, for sure.
I hope so.
Thank you, Yunus Emre.
Thank you. If Allah permits, it will be as you say.
Well, you've filled our bag again.
Now we should go.
But we always expect to see you in Yenisehir.
Be my guest. You will be treated properly.
If Allah permits, Osman Bey. I will try to come.
Well... Have a safe journey.
Thank you.
-Alps, peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Cerkutay.
I knew you would come here.
Hasan.
I'm Cerkutay. Don't you recognize me?
Shahzade Alaaddin's orders.
Nobody will pass.
Stay back. Let me inform him.
You don't know me, Hasan. If I want to go in,
...I go in.
What's going on here?
-My Shahzade. -Alaaddin.
Put your swords down. -Look at that.
Impertinent Alaaddin.
You will die too. Just be patient.
What are you doing here, Cerkutay Bey?
-Cerkutay, don't.
-Bayindir Bey.
My Shahzade.
-Speak.
-I have information for you.
Yakup Bey is after the princess.
He has sent good trackers around.
I found first and brought the news to you.
You need to change location.
Did they realize? Brother, they look worried.
Will we really trust Cerkutay?
We trust nobody, sister.
We'll follow and jump on them.
Cerkutay was the scouting dog. He did his duty.
Now we will see if the princess is here.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
This is the second time you
are an uninvited guest, Amir.
If don't wait for the
invitation in the third time
...you will see a different side of me.
I don't wait for invitation from
somewhere I already own, Sultan Yakup.
Now tell me.
What is your answer to my offer?
Will you bring the princess to me...
...and stay away from my wrath?
Or choose to vanish with Osman...
..in the frontiers?
Equating me with Osman
would do no good for you, Amir.
I'm the sultan of this land. I
never make a move with a threat.
Sultan Yakup, don't you see?
Osman is gathering all the
Turkish beys around himself.
And you are staying alone.
Sultans are always alone, Amir.
This is not something new.
However, they are alone
when they are standing straight.
They have a lot of people with
them when they are on the ground.
After Osman's acts..
..your people will leave you too, Sultan Yakup.
Do you know what will happen..
..after I marry with the princess?
Ilkhanate's power will grow.
Why should I get in between you and Osman..
..just because Ilkhanate will gain power?
Because if you bring me the princess..
..you will be allies with Ilkhanids.
My power will be your power.
If you say no,
my spies in your lands await news from me.
To be a friend to a friend..
..and a foe to a foe.
Then, send the word, Emir.
Since you came to our door with good intentions..
..I will not refuse.
I will bring the princess to you.
You are on the right path, Yakup.
May your Sultanate live long.
You are on the right path.
Did anyone follow you?
I don't think so. I was
cautious my bey, however..
Shall we increase the alps, my shahzade?
No. If we increase the
alps, we will draw suspicion.
Increasing the scouts on
the roads would be enough.
We will reach our destination.
If we can have this princess,
we can make both mongols..
..and Byzantine do as we say.
If Allah permits, my brother.
If Allah permits. However, princess might not be here.
Princess is here.
If not, then Alaeddin wouldn't be
here. Cerkutay wouldn't have come here.
Bayindir Bey, I will leave now.
The princess is in your hands.
-Be cautious.
-As you command, my shahzade.
You told me you brought everything, Bayindir Bey.
Princess is here.
One of my chests is missing.
There must be a confusion.
I will have it checked at once.
You?
Are you leaving, Shahzade Alaeddin?
Bayindir Bey will accompany you.
Will you come back?
I will, as soon as possible.
The weather is bad do not get cold.
Come on alps!
My mother is wrong, Gonca.
This Alaeddin does not love you.
They are looking for either a Lord's daughter..
..or a princess as brides.
You are right.
However, this is not the issue.
Tell me when will you catch this princess.
We are few, my Gonca.
They have everywhere guarded.
If we ambush them now, we will lose.
Then, we must inform our
father and come back with alps.
However, we also need to watch them.
It is not certain what they will do.
-My brother, should I stay here?
-No.
We know their location.
Leaving two alps will suffice.
We will go together. Come on.
Oh praise be! It does not surprise me.
-Are you alright?
-Thank Allah, my bey.
Father.
My Osman Bey.
-My son.
This is not the time.
We will talk later.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
You are saying you accepted Gorklu Khan's offer.
However, can we trust him, Yakup Bey?
Never.
However, being allies with us now..
..benefits him.
He knows we will find the
princess before anyone else.
What about us? How will it benefits us..
..after Gorklu Khan marries the princess?
We will be allies with Ilkhanids and Byzantine..
..for a while.
I will have Osman live..
..in misery like he never had before.
The beys that stood behind him
will come to my side one by one.
No one will dare to challenge me again.
What about Holofira? Will we not
have them answer for our bride?
Of course we will.
However, let us first wait for
Gonca and Mehmed to come back.
-Are we allowed, my father? -Come in.
Tell me, what is the situation?
-Did you find the princess?
-We did, father.
I memorized their place. I
left two alps there just in case.
Good, you thought good.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Sultan.
Send word to Gorklu Khan. We found the princess.
She will be in our hands
tomorrow at the very least.
As you command, my Sultan.
Mehmed, Gonca.
You take the alps and go
where princess is being held.
Bring the princess here as soon as possible.
We will ruin Osman's trickery.
As you command, my father.
However, if you see fit..
..let my sister stay here.
I do not run away from my duty, brother.
I know, my sister. You fight
better than the mightiest soldier.
However, you should be tired.
There are many alps, we can handle it.
What is it Mehmed? Did something happen?
No, mother. It is nothing.
Let me tell you what it is.
He does not want to take me with him
because Alaeddin Bey is with the princess.
If you insist on coming, I will
start to think it is because of him.
However my father sees fit.
Mehmed will go with his alps.
And you will stay here.
And we will do an important
visit with your mother.
Osman thinks he formed a beylic.
Now he declares himself as "The Ottoman".
Today is the day to show him that he is nothing.
Mehmed, go and take that princess.
As you command, my father. I will have
that princess even if it costs my life.
-Am I allowed, my Sultan?
-Come in.
My Sultan. Orhan and
Holofira arrived at Yenisehir.
I know what to do with them.
Hatun, get ready. We will leave soon.
Allah's mercy shall be upon you.
My Allah..
My Allah, my Allah, my Allah...
I am at Your door, my Allah.
May You show mercy to this poor subject of Yours.
I am walking on this way to
make the dream of the state...
..I had come true, my Allah.
As I walk, I encounter many obstacles...
...many oppressors, and many enemies.
To defeat them, I trust...
...and take refuge in You
alone, my Allah. My Allah...
May You give me power
and strength to defeat my...
...secret enemies and other
enemies that I know, my Allah.
My Allah...
You are the One Who makes enemies friends...
...and friends enemies, my Allah.
May You give unity and order to
my people and my family, my Allah...
I know...
I know that...
Those who have big dreams...
...encounter big and difficult tests.
My Allah..
Do not turn my dreams into a burden,
make them turn into my companion...
Turn them into a companion, my Allah...
May You grant me with...
...the honesty I need to be on the straight path.
Accept our prayers, my Allah. Aameen.
I will turn this palace into my
barn after everything is over.
Keep your intentions and anger
hidden, my friend. We are at their table.
Lord! Let us hear what you are saying.
You'll learn when the time comes.
Attention! Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Welcome... Welcome. Welcome.
You may sit.
If you keep sharpening your
swords against each other...
...then... It will be inevitable
for us to get killed...
...by Mongols.
Tell me. Have you investigated this matter?
My contact in Constantinople confirms
the information you provided, Osman Bey.
So... What we know is true.
I can't understand how the
Emperor did this, Osman Bey.
In these lands, agreements are written in blood.
The Emperor wants to
protect himself and his power..
...with you.
Thus, he is sacrificing you.
Mongols...
..will crush us.
And as a reward, they will take your heads...
...and your lands. You should know that.
But as long as you keep
the Princess in your hands
the agreement will not
be finalized, Osman Bey.
Great Roman Lords owe their lives to a Turk, huh?
Do you think we cannot defeat Mongols?
They can never go beyond our walls!
Lord Leon..
Mongols must never hear your fearless words.
While you rust in your palace...
...they live in the steppes and moorland.
And you are also saying that
they cannot climb over your walls.
Then tell me.
Semerkand, Konya and Baghdad...
Didn't those places have walls? Tell me.
Apparently, you..
...don't even know...
...who you are fighting against.
Everyone is responsible of their people.
But... The situation is obvious.
We don't have much time.
And those Mongols will not show mercy to anyone.
They will crush them. Therefore...
...when we still have time, I am telling you...
Bow down before me.
If you accept...
...I will consider your people as my own people.
I will protect them.
Don't forget... From now on....
..there is a state here.
And your future...
...is under our sanjak.
If I was not mad at the Emperor,
I would never accept that.
I am with you, Osman Bey.
-We are with you, Osman Bey.
-Thank you, thank you.
We are with you Osman Bey!
Oh praise be!... Thank you.
Thank you...
If Allah permits we will unite under one sanjak.
And... we will stay there forever.
-Boran!
-My Bey.
Come on. Play your qopuz.
-Yes my Bey.
Can I come in, my Osman Bey?
Come in, Baysungur.
My Bey. Your guests...
Aunt..
Osman Bey! I am Olivia.
I am Holofira's aunt.
And you will give my niece back to me now.
Or else, I will destroy this city.
-Stop there, Hatun!
Are you threatening us in the palace
you entered without permission?
How are you going to do
the thing you just said, huh?
With me.
She will destroy it with me.
Do you have any other questions?
We thought someone was missing...
And now he is here.
Welcome, Yakup Bey.
Alaeddin... Alaeddin!
-When did they notice you?
-Once you left, my Shahzade.
They noticed from the very beginning.
I will kill that Cerkutay!
Gokmen! -My Shahzade...
Send Alps everywhere! We will find them!
Yes my Shahzade.
We will find that Princess
no matter what happens.
No matter what!
The trace we left will keep
Mehmet far away from us.
He cannot find any traces to come here.
But they will not give up.
If not today, tomorrow.
How long can we hide the Princess?
Forever, if necessary, brother.
This Princses is the soft spot
of Byzantines and Mongols,
the two biggest power.
May Allah forbid, if this
marriage is going to happen
we will be ruined. But as
long as we keep the Princess
both Osman Bey and his Beylik will get stronger.
Come on.
You kidnapped my future
daughter-in-law, on top of that
you lost her to
Mongols as hostage
and as if it's not enough, do
you keep her as a hostage now?
Calm down, Yakup Bey.
Who are we keeping as hostage in our palace?
If something had happened
to Holofira after all this
you'd pay for it heavily.
Don't worry, as long as I am with her
no one can hurt Holofira.
Is there any greater harm to her than you, Orhan?
Hatun, pick your words carefully.
We do not hurt anyone.
If you do not test our patience, of course.
Aunt, please.
Come on, daughter. Let's go.
Yakup Bey.
Who are you taking from our palace?
Do you want me to cut your head, Osman Bey?
Just try it.
Osman!
Holofira will leave if she wants to leave.
But it is up to her.
I will not stay here any longer.
But I will not come with you as well, Yakup Bey.
I'll go back with my aunt.
Now are you having Lords
at your table, Osman Bey?
Your treason has been exposed.
I'm not on the same path as you.
On one side, there is a man who does everything
and does every move.
But on the other side, there's
a man who only threatens
and blocks every move.
The history will write the truth for sure.
Too pity.
History will only write about
your treason, Osman Bey.
My path is clear.
My cause is clear.
Keep that in your mind, on this path
I will show no mercy to anyone I come across
I'll crush him down.
You're right.
We're not on the same path.
Come on, have a safe journey.
Come on.
You have called me, Hadhrat Emir.
Your nokers
lost Orhan.
You came empty-handed. Now tell me.
Why wouldn't I burn you all in fire
Karacelasun?
What are you going to give me except for defeat?
Osman is taking beys' support.
-He's getting stronger.
-Is that all?
He will make his move with the Lords.
Osman intents to make Byzantines attack us.
Are you afraid?
Are you afraid that you will end up
like your brother?
Weren't you here for vengeance, Karacelasun?
Are you going to cry like a woman?
I've never felt fear in my heart.
I have enough power to
destroy Osman, those behind him
and anyone who come towards us!
Hadhrat Emir. We have news from Yakup Bey.
They found the Princess. They
will capture her in the morning.
Yakup. Sultan Yakup.
He does everything to remain Sultan.
Very well. Yakup will bring me the Princess.
When will my army in Konya arrive?
Tong Chu.
-They will be here by the morning, Hadhrat Emir.
-Very well.
When my army arrives, they
will leave for their first duty.
Since Osman is playing tricks against us
I'll bring Osman to hell.
And you will capture the
beyliks that are loyal to Osman.
You will burn their tribes and destroy them.
It is your last chance
Not a single one of them
will be able to help Osman,
they will be in need of help, Hadhrat Emir.
By sunrise you will have surrounded the beyliks.
Karacelasun, gather your nokers.
I'll do as you
order, Hadhrat Emir.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
-Come on now, open the map.
-Yes, my Bey.
Praise be.
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.
Here, the borders of our Beylik
starts here, goes forward
and goes all the way to the here.
Paths and routes here...
...are under our control.
No one without paying taxes
and without permissions will be able to enter.
Everyone, my Bey?
Everyone who is not
under our command.
Candar, Karesi
and Germiyan.
-It doesn't matter.
-Yes, my Bey.
From now on, we will collect
taxes from the Lords as well.
So there will be a lot of
transfers in and out of the treasury.
As the chief treasurer,
Bayindir Bey will deal with the treasury.
Inform him.
Yes, my Bey.
Also, write this down.
Malhun Hatun, now, Lords agreed
to take the goods to Yenisehir.
Some will even bring the
goods from Constantinople.
So the Yenisehir marketplace...
-...is under your responsibility.
-Yes, my Bey.
We are fighting a total war.
When alps go to the battle, the lands and tribes
will be defenseless
So, that is why
the protection of the Lords
is also our responsibility.
So we cannot let that happen.
Bala Hatun.
You will turn Sogut into
the headquarter of Sisters.
They will have absolute resistance
against any kind of cruelty.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Thank you.
We need to send a judge and a
teacher to each tribe in no time.
-Write this down too.
-As you order, my Bey.
What about the borders, my
Bey? Won't we expand them?
Well, son... This is one of the laws of a beylic.
The one that doesn't expand has to become arrow.
Now... Our destination will be Kite.
Then I will provide alps and
food from Kestel to Kite, my Bey.
You won't, Orhan.
Kestel..
...isn't your property anymore.
Karacahisar isn't your property either.
You need to deserve them first.
Your latest mistakes caused too many troubles.
As Osman Bey orders.
The council is over! Bala Hatun
Malhun Hatun. You two stay.
You may leave.
Today, we will avenge...
...all the Mongolians who died in the frontiers!
You, the savages of Amir Coban!
My loyal nokers!
We will make the blood of Turks flow in rivers!
I will take Osman's heart out.
Here we go! We're holding hell in our hands!
Get ready to burn everywhere!
Attention! Osman Bey!
My Bey, all the alps are
ready to go on a campaign.
Okay, okay.
My alps! My brave warriors!
My solid-hearted lions!
Our becoming a state in the frontiers
has driven the enemy completely mad!
Jackals disguised as sheep
have already showed their teeth!
The Lord of Kite is only one of them.
After we defeat him, Bursa and
Iznik will be the next. For this reason,
...we will crush the Lord of Kite!
We’ll overcome the obstacles one
by one and maintain order in the world.
Alps! We perform campaigns!
Allah provides victory!
-Allah is the greatest!
-Allah is the greatest, Allah is the greatest!
May your campaign be blessed, my Bey.
May your fight be holy, my
Bey. Come back with good news.
Thank you. Thank you. I trust you for Yenisehir.
Father, let me go with you.
I've been training for long.
My dear daughter. I'm going on a campaign now.
But when I'm back, we will train together.
I will make my decision according to that.
Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
Yakup Bey won't stop chasing the princess.
-Keep your eye on him.
-As my Bey orders.
I won't let them find the princess
at the cost of my life, father.
Thank you, thank you.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
Well... If the enemy hear
that we're out of Yenisehir
...they may attack here.
Take some alps with you
and wait in a middle spot.
You will strike in case they attempt to attack.
As you order, my Bey. I
will strike like a thunder!
Thank you, thank you.
Come on then. It's time for campaign!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Aunt, what do you mean I won't go to the
frontier market again? I have an agreement.
It's over. Your agreement is over.
You'll close your shop in the
frontier market. From now on
...you won't go to the frontier
market or Yenisehir again.
-But why?
-Are you even asking, Holofira?
Have you forgotten what you went through?
First Orhan, then Mongolians...
I can't put you in danger anymore.
But it wasn't Orhan's fault.
Don't defend a man who can't
protect you. This is my final words.
You won't get out of the castle anymore.
-My lady, we got a letter for you.
-Get out.
Aunt, for the last time, just let me go...
No. You won't leave the castle.
Orhan. You made me worry, son.
I had no other options, mother.
Mehmed on one side and
Holofira's aunt on the other.
And... And you.
Mother, Holofira needs some time to be a Muslim.
-Before we teach her Islam...
-Teach her then, son.
I have plenty of time.
I can wait.
But don't you blame me for this issue.
You don't accept Holofira, mother.
You leave me no other options.
See? I've lost my mission.
You lost your mission because
of your own mistake, Orhan Bey.
This is what exactly I tried to tell you.
You are a bey. You should think a thousand
times and make one move like a bey.
I'm being late for my duty, mother.
Excuse me.
Holofira s love causes you
to make mistakes, Orhan.
If I have made a mistake,
...I will pay the price, mother.
You are the fire. And Holofira is the wind.
This wind will only make the fire grow bigger.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
You should find the princess no matter what.
I will bring her back this time, father.
Gonca, this mission is yours.
Don't send Gonca, father.
Alaaddin is holding the princess.
-If you...
-How dare you speak words...
...against mine, Mehmed?
You have another duty.
You will bring intelligence...
..about Osman.
-As you order, father.
-Come on. Everybody get to their duties.
Change your way when
you see impertinent Alaaddin.
You won't speak to him, Gonca. Do you get it?
Why are you giving Gonca such duties, Yakup Bey?
I'm testing my daughter, hatun.
She achieved her first duty.
She took the merchants from Bala Hatun.
If she achieves this too..
If she brings the princess
to me despite Alaaddin...
What will you do then, Yakup Bey?
-Welcome, Bala Hatun.
-Thank you.
-Welcome Bala Hatun.
-May your work be easy.
-Mother.
-Yes?
-Where is brother Alaaddin?
-He’s on duty, dear.
-Dealing with our guest.
-He's gone after Gonca Hatun.
-He must be in the frontier market.
-You shut up.
Bala Hatun. Forgive me, but...
...your son is my rival now.
-Really?
-I'm going!
Where are you going? Where?
Her demon mother doesn't ever
let her marry Shahzade Alaaddin.
You think you can marry her, Ghazi?
Why doesn't she let her marry Shahzade?
A girl's family play hard
to get, Ghazi Alp. We'll see.
-If she doesn't let...
-I will kidnap her! Even before Shahzade!
But I need coins and more training.
-I'm going!
-All you need is coins and training, Ghazi.
I'll take him to the palace. He is misbehaving.
Mother. Will we really snatch
Gonca Hatun if they don't give her up?
We will see. If we will snatch
her or get her father's permission.
Time will tell.
-You will be a mother to her as well, right?
-Should I?
-You should.
-Alright I will a little.
Osman Bey is coming!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
-What's the situation?
-Alps are repairing battering ram for the door.
The army would be ready
to move until midafternoon.
Alright, alright, alright.
My Bey. We just came to an agreement yesterday.
I know Lord can not be trusted.
However, wouldn't a move like
this draw us away from other lords?
The Lord of Kite is not my target
because his tongue is not still.
-But because of his treachery.
-Do we know something, my bey?
He told everything to the
Lords of Iznik and Bursa.
They took orders from them
and came to an agreement with us.
He will strike us from behind
in the first chance he gets.
Not only this, he also wants
to cooperate with Yakup Bey.
I won't even make a guard dog out of those..
..who become slaves to our enemies.
Now, we will distribute
the treasure of Kite to lords.
-And they will keep their mouths shut.
-Okay, my bey.
Someone's coming!
-Peace be upon you Osman Bey.
-Peace be upon you Solgur Aga.
Praise be.
You are welcomed.
In this glorious war path..
..I brought valiant warriors.
All of whom a lion each,
..trained by Gaziyan. We are ready for war.
Praise be, praise be!
We will win many conquests..
..many wars and victories thanks to them.
“May Gaziyans live long.
“If Allah permits Osman Bey, If Allah permits.
Konur.
-Yes, my bey.
-We will be at Kite..
..before midafternoon.
-Now, finish your preparations.
-As you command, my bey.
They must've left a track.
We will look thoroughly sisters.
We will find that princess.
Come on sisters, look everywhere!
Guice, send two alps behind Alaeddin
Bey. They shall follow him cautiously.
-As you command, Gonca Hatun.
-Come on.
I do not get followed, Trickster Hatun.
-Alaeddin Bey.
-Welcome, Coy Hatun.
You just couldn't fall back.
So we really had to be square.
-Tell me, what are
you doing here?
Yakup Bey is
after the princess.
He has skilled scouts. They're all around.
You are after the princess.
I saw you yesterday. I knew
you would be back to track us.
Right, I am after the princess.
And what are you after?
She must be really worried about you.
Go along then, don't keep her worried!
What is it? Are you
jealous of me?
Jealous Hatun.
What happened? Are you hurt? Sorry.
It is duty, don't be jealous.
My eyes are blind to others than you.
My ears do not hear others but you.
If you ask about this heart
of mine? It is already tied up.
You hit hard, Jealous Hatun.
Our duties put us against each
other time and time again Alaeddin.
This will always be like
that. You know that right?
No. It won't be always like this.
All will be well, after we get married.
What if they don't? Alaeddin
what if blood gets between us?
Hold on.
Don't invite the bad things. We
shall think good so it may be good.
We will get married.
-Alaeddin!
-Brother!
Who will you marry with?
Brother! Stop, what are you doing?
Brother!
Take all of their heads! Burn
their houses to the ground!
Attack!
Archers, get in position!
Soldiers, defend the people quickly!
Ignite the beacons!
Everyone who stand behind
Osman will burn in my flame!
This tribe will be your grave, mongol!
This and other tribes will be
slain by mongols' mighty swords!
Attack on the tribes has already
started! I am your destiny now!
-Battering ram is ready, my bey.
-Okay.
-Konur.
-Yes, my bey.
You will lead the siege. You
will climb the walls with ladders.
Boran, alps and me.
We will ram the backdoor.
-With the battering ram.
-As you command, my bey.
It's from my patrols. Mongol
dastards attacked Uraz Bey's tribe.
Patrols tried to stop them, but...
No one but us will help us.
Take the siege equipment to the forest.
We will go to the tribe.
You forgot about us while Osman was here.
Now Ilkhanids are here, where is Osman?
-You will be ruined.
-Osman Bey is not here!
But brave soldiers of Turks are here!
The fate of death was
written when my brother died.
I'll ruin your houses. You will bend the knee.
You will die.
-Never!
Yenisehir is not even the size
of Ilkhanid's hunting ground.
This is a rebellion against the God of Death.
Osman, both you and your city will be ruined!
Braveheart nokers of Ilkhanids.
You fought by my side in China,
in the mountain of Tengri.
You captured their treasures and castles!
Now we will teach these lands
the glory of nokers
and strength of Ilkhanids! We will destroy
the capital city of Osman
who captured the princess.
Their women and their children
will be ruined!
Emir Gorklu Khan, Osman set out for the tribe.
Great. Let him go to his tribe.
Get ready. We're starting.
The city is very well protected.
-How are you going to enter?
-First,
you will disguise as them.
I'll attack with my nokers
when the adhan sounds. The rest is blood
the rest is doomsday!
-Brother, don't!
-Let go off me Gonca!
Brother, stop. Alaeddin!
Brother, stop. Brother, stop. Please don't.
-For Allah's sake, don't.
-Let go off me Gonca!
I'll talk to you later.
Do not say anything to her.
Tell me what you have to say.
Who are you to try to protect my sister?
Alaeddin, please.
Alaeddin, no. Brother, for Allah's sake.
I'm in love with your sister, Mehmed Bey.
It is my responsibility to protect her life.
Alaeddin! Brother!
Alaeddin, please stop.
-Brother, no!
-Move away, Gonca!
I'll not see you around my sister, Alaeddin!
Just calm down.
Just listen to me.
-Gonca! Move away, Gonca!
-No!
No! Brother! Brother! Alaeddin.
Brother, stop. Brother, stop.
-Alps, help me! -Gokmen! Arrest them!
No! No! No! Alaeddin, no.
-Stop it, Mehmed Bey!
-Hold Gonca!
Brother! no!
-Don't do it, Mehmed Bey.
-I said no, brother!
Who's going to save you from me now, Alaeddin?
You're testing my patience,
Mehmed Bey. Let Gonca go.
Your problem is with me.
Brother, please stop it! Stop it! Alaeddin!
Brother, please. Brother, what are you doing?
-Brother, please!
-No.
I've told you many times that you will
change your path when you see Alaeddin.
-Brother, stop!
-You wanted this, Gonca.
Alaeddin! Brother!
Let go off me! Alaeddin!
You spilled the blood of my alps and people
-you will pay for this!
-I don't pay price.
I burned down their tribes
and I ruined their cities.
I didn't even leave a child who can seek revenge!
I will make you pay for this!
No, now you will die.
Osman Bey.
Osman, I've been waiting for you.
You will not be able to
invade Turks' independence!
-Ya Allah!
-Allah!
Our men have stood against the
oppressors! Kill them with your swords...
...until we defeat all the demons, my valiants!
Alps! Today, death will not find
us but it will find them! Come on!
-Peace be upon you!
-Peace be upon you too!
What is in the cart?
-Clothes.
Let us see.
Alright, you can go. -Thank you.
It is time, get ready.
Gorklu Khan will bring
death to this city, come on!
Run!
Mother!
Take the elderly and children to
places where they can take shelter!
Do not let them enter the
palace! Inform Malhun! Come on!
Kill everyone on whom...
...Osman's shadow falls!
We will bring the doomsday here today!
Attack!
Fatma... Go back to the palace.
My homeland is raided, mother.
You are telling me to go back.
I can fight with a sword.
Good. Stay behind me.
We can give our lives, but never
the lands we took with martyrs' blood!
Alps! Come on!
Alps! We will stop Mongols
before they approach the palace.
Gorkem! Make a defense wall in the streets.
Position archers on the top, come on!
Yes, Baysungur Alp!
-Come on! Hurry!
Baysungur Alp. The
people are taking refuge in
shelters. The Mongols
have seized the marketplace.
That is not good.
Inform our Alps. Tell them to retreat,
fighting all the way back to the defense line.
Come on! Alps! Listen to me! Come here!
Today, with Allah's consent,
we will not let Mongols pass.
Once they reach the defense line, we
will attack and destroy them If Allah permits
Come on! Now everyone go back to their duties!
Baysungur! What happened? What is the situation?
Mongols... They sneaked in the
city under the guise of our people.
-What?
-They are coming here fast.
First... first, our people.
Their safety will be ensured.
Ulgen. Fulfill all of our
Alps' and Sisters' needs.
Bring the injured ones here. And inform Fatma.
Malhun Hatun... Fatma is
at the marketplace with Bala.
What are you saying, Ulgen?
Alps! Sisters! We are
going to the marketplace!
Malhun Hatun!
The marketplace has fallen.
They surrounded it from all sides.
My Allah...
-Malhun Hatun..
My Allah, protect
them.. Protect them.
Come here!
Allah is the Greatest! Allah is the Greatest!
You thoughtyou Would be
saved after taking the Princess
You thought you would be
saved after taking the Princess.
But disaster is raining on your lands.
These lands were taken with
blood! And they are kept with blood!
How will you save them Osman?
Your tribes and cities are destroyed!
Alps will arrive! Cities will
be built! But independence...
...independence is the legacy of Turks!
This tribe will be your hell, Osman!
You will find independence after you die!
Whether we stand united or are left
alone, we will never give up these lands!
Ya Allah!
I swear, I swear..
I will wipe you out from these lands!
Just because you oppressed my people like this...
If I do not bury you in these lands,
they must not call me Osman Bey!
Visit turkision.com for more!